[upbeat music]
[both] 28, 29, 30.
Guess we're tied.
看来我们打平了。
We got the same number of Valentines.
我们的情人节卡片数量一样多。
Boom!
砰！
Read 'em and weep, losers.
读读看，哭吧，输家们。
Looks like I won the Valentime's contest.
看来我赢了情人节比赛。
Did you just say Valentime's?
你刚才是说Valentime's吗？
Yeah, that's what it's called.
对，就是那么叫的。
No, it's not.
不，不是的。
It's Valentine's.
是情人节。
That's ridiculous.
这太荒谬了。
It's the time that dude Valen
这是那个叫Valen的家伙
comes and shoots people with his bone and marrow.
来用他的骨头和骨髓射人的时候。
It's bow and arrow.
是弓箭。
Now you're just making stuff up.
你现在只是在编造东西。
It's official. I'm the big winner.
这是官方的。我是大赢家。
Check out what I got from Mae.
看看我从Mae那里得到了什么。
[Mae on recording] Mae you have a happy Valentine's Day!
Mae祝你情人节快乐！
Mae you have a happy Valentine's Day!
Just because you have one really cool card
仅仅因为你有一张非常酷的卡片
doesn't mean that you win.
并不意味着你就赢了。
Oh, really?
哦，真的吗？
What do you think, Mae?
你怎么看，Mae？
Dawn wins! Dawn wins!
Dawn赢了！Dawn赢了！
No.
不。
Dicky wins. Dicky wins.
Dicky赢了。Dicky赢了。
No.
不。
Hey, look. I found one more.
嘿，看。我又找到了一张。
[Dicky and Dawn arguing]
[Dicky和Dawn争吵]
You wrote that to yourself.
你这是写给自己的吧。
Oh, you want to dance?
哦，你想跳舞吗？
Let's dance.
来跳舞吧。
[all shouting]
（大家都在喊）
- Kids! Kids!
孩子们！孩子们！
Stop fighting!
别打了！
Mae, this is nothing to smile about.
梅，这没什么好笑的。
Um, Ms. Harvell?
嗯，哈维尔女士？
Oh. Sorry.
哦。对不起。
You know, I think you're all losing sight
你知道吗，我觉得你们都忽略了
of what Valentine's Day is all about.
你们都忘记了情人节的意义。
It's about what you give, not what you get.
它关乎你给予什么，而非你得到什么。
Excuse me. Delivery.
不好意思，有快递。
Oh, look what I get!
哦，看我得到了什么！
Are you Mrs. Grundle?
您是Grundle夫人吗？
No, but I could be Mrs. Delivery Man.
不是，但我可以是快递先生的夫人。
Like I said, kids, it's not about what you get.
就像我说的，孩子们，重点不在于你们得到什么。
In fact, I am going to give you all a little assignment.
实际上，我要给你们所有人一个小任务。
[all groaning]
[大家都在抱怨]
You don't need to give us anything.
您不需要给我们任何东西。
You know, we are so good.
你知道，我们真的很棒。
I'd like you all to make Valentine's Day
我希望你们每个人都能为某个人
really special for someone other than yourselves.
特别地庆祝情人节。
Then, Monday, you'll give an oral report
然后，周一，你们要做一个口头报告
on the effect it had on that person.
关于这对那个人的影响。
Oh, yes, Mae. You had a question?
哦，是的，梅。你有问题吗？
Still not me.
还不是我。
I'm just gonna go close the card.
我只是去把卡片关上。
[Ricky] Yeah.
[Ricky] 是的。
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
♪ ♪
[man] [whistling melody]
（男人）（吹口哨旋律）
♪ ♪
[rhythmic clapping] - ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
（有节奏的拍手声）- ♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
[man] [whistling melody]
（男人）（吹口哨旋律）
♪ ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na-na ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐呐 ♪
- ♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na ♪
- ♪ 一，二 ♪ - ♪ 呐，呐，呐 ♪
[man] ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
（男人）♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
Hey, Anne.
嘿，Anne。
Are you pumped for our big Valentine's Day sale?
你对我们的大规模情人节促销感到兴奋吗？
Huh?
嗯？
No, I'm not pumped.
不，我不兴奋。
There's nobody in the store.
店里没人。
And you know why?
你知道为什么吗？
Everyone's out buying candy and stuffed bears.
大家都在外面买糖果和毛绒熊。
Honey, no guy is dumb enough
亲爱的，没有哪个男人会傻到
to give his wife a treadmill for Valentine's Day.
在情人节送他妻子一台跑步机。
Not if we don't make it look fun!
如果我们不把它弄得看起来有趣的话！
- Hmm. [treadmill beeping]
嗯。[跑步机发出哔哔声]
Huh? Fun, right?
啊？有趣，对吧？
Okay, that's a little fast.
好吧，有点太快了。
[beeping] Slow it down.
[哔哔声] 慢下来。
[beeping and thumping]
[哔哔声和砰砰声]
Anne, a little help.
安妮，帮个忙。
- Oh. - [shouts]
哦。
[Anne] Tom!
[安妮] 汤姆！
Oh!
哦！
Okay, let's just get
好吧，我们先把这次情人节的任务搞定。
this Valentime's assignment over with.
让我们赶紧完成这个情人节的任务。
I guess we could just pick a random customer in the store.
我想我们可以随便在店里选一个顾客。
[cricket chirping]
[蟋蟀鸣叫]
We're all hearing that cricket, right?
我们都听到那只蟋蟀的叫声，对吧？
[Ricky] Mm-hmm.
[Ricky] 嗯哼。
Oh, how about Josie?
哦，乔西怎么样？
She's always doing nice things for us.
她总是为我们做好事。
Plus, she looks really bored, so--
而且，她看起来真的很无聊，所以——
- Yeah.
- 是的。
Oh. Hey, guys.
哦。嘿，伙计们。
[Dicky] Hey, Josie.
嘿，Josie。
You're always so good to us,
你总是对我们这么好，
so we want to return the favor for Valentime's Day.
所以我们在情人节想回报你一下。
Seriously?
真的吗？
Is that not bothering anybody else?
这不会让其他人感到困扰吗？
Oh, that's sweet but not necessary.
哦，那很贴心，但没必要。
I actually have my first Valentine's date!
实际上，我有了第一个情人节约会！
- Wilson finally asked you? - Uh-huh!
Wilson终于约你了？
[both squealing]
嗯哼！
But we still want to do something nice for you.
但我们还是想为你做点好事。
How about we help get you ready?
我们帮你准备怎么样？
We'll start with the nails.
我们从指甲开始。
Why? What's wrong with my nails?
为什么？我的指甲有什么问题吗？
I think she meant your hair.
我想她指的是你的头发。
What's wrong with my hair?
我的头发怎么了？
With all that makeup,
化了那么多妆，
I don't think anyone will notice the hair.
我想没人会注意到头发的。
My makeup too?
我的妆也要改？
Yeah, the whole thing's a hot mess.
对，整个造型一团糟。
Oh, no.
哦，不。
I have so much work to do for tomorrow night.
我明天晚上有很多工作要做。
Tell your parents I'm taking the night off.
告诉你父母我今晚休息。
All right. Assignment done.
好吧。作业完成了。
We didn't do anything.
我们什么都没做。
We have to do something for someone.
我们得为某人做点什么。
[cricket chirping]
[蟋蟀鸣叫]
Oh, maybe find a date for the cricket.
哦，也许可以给蟋蟀找个约会对象。
[crunch]
[嘎吱声]
Or not.
或者不。
Face it, Tom.
面对现实吧，汤姆。
Valentine's Day is always a disaster.
情人节总是个灾难。
It's our worst day of the year.
这是我们一年中最糟糕的一天。
- You're right, Anne.
你说得对，安妮。
I don't even know why we try.
我甚至不知道我们为什么要尝试。
[sighs]
（叹气）
Stupid Valentine's Day.
愚蠢的情人节。
[grunts]
（咕哝）
[panting]
（喘气）
Oh, hey, kids.
哦，嘿，孩子们。
- Hey, Dad. - Hi, Dad.
嘿，爸爸。 - 嗨，爸爸。
- That's weird.
- 真奇怪。
Mom and Dad don't like Valentine's Day?
妈妈和爸爸不喜欢情人节吗？
Come to think of it,
仔细想想，
every year, all they do is go to work,
每年，他们只是去上班，
come home angry, and hang out with us.
回家时生气，然后和我们待在一起。
Then that's our assignment.
那么这就是我们的任务了。
Give Mom and Dad a Valentine's Day they'll like.
给爸爸妈妈一个他们喜欢的情人节。
But to do that, first we have to find out why they don't like it.
但要做到这一点，首先我们必须找出他们为什么不喜欢它。
[popping]
[pop]
And fast.
而且要快。
[Dawn] All right, spread out.
[Dawn] 好了，分散找找。
There's got to be something in there
那里一定有什么东西
that'll help us figure out why Mom and Dad hate Valentine's Day.
能帮我们弄清楚为什么爸妈讨厌情人节。
[Dicky] Oh, guys, I found something.
[Dicky] 哦，伙计们，我找到了点东西。
Bubble wrap!
气泡膜！
[all] Yeah!
[大家] 耶！
[popping]
[挤压声]
Whoo.
哇哦。
[Ricky] [sighs]
[Ricky] [叹气]
All right, now that we got that out of our systems,
好了，现在我们发泄完了
keep looking.
继续找
Hey.
嘿
I bet there's something in this box
我打赌这个标着“情意绵绵的东西”的盒子里有东西
marked "Lovey-Dovey Stuff."
哦。哇
[Dawn] Oh. Ooh.
这里有一堆旧情人节卡片
Here are a bunch of old Valentine's cards.
看到了吧
See?
爸妈并不讨厌情人节
Mom and Dad don't hate Valentine's Day.
哦，这还有一些情书
Oh, and here's some love letters.
他们接吻的照片
[groans]
[呻吟声]
Pictures of them kissing.
他们接吻的照片。
[gags]
[作呕声]
[Dawn] Oh, and here's something dated February 14, 2004.
[Dawn] 哦，这里有一些2004年2月14日的。
That's Valentine's Day from right before we were born.
那是在我们出生之前的一个情人节。
[all] Whoa!
[所有人] 哇！
What is that thing?
那是什么东西？
I'm not quite sure.
我不太确定。
[rattling] - Where's the "on" button?
[摇晃声] - 开机键在哪里？
There isn't one. It's a videotape.
没有开机键。这是录像带。
A video what?
视频什么？
Dad comes up here with a case of root beer
爸爸会带着一箱根啤上来
and watches his old ice dancing competitions on this TV.
然后在这台电视上看他以前的冰舞比赛。
That's a TV?
那是台电视？
I put a burrito in there last week.
我上周把一个玉米卷放里面了。
No wonder it didn't cook it.
难怪没烤熟。
Whoa, it swallowed it.
哇，它吞了。
Okay. Here we go.
好吧。我们开始吧。
[chuckles softly]
[轻声笑]
[gasps] There they are, Tom.
[吸气] 他们在这儿，汤姆。
[Anne] All four of them.
[Anne] 他们四个都在。
[Tom] Wow, this is really happening.
[Tom] 哇，这真的发生了。
We're having quadruplets.
我们要有四胞胎了。
You know what this means, Tom?
你知道这意味着什么吗，Tom？
Valentine's Day is ruined.
情人节毁了。
Forever.
永远毁了。
[Tom] It sure is.
[Tom] 确实如此。
I can't believe this.
我简直不敢相信。
This is our fault.
这是我们的错。
We ruined Valentine's Day for Mom and Dad.
我们毁了爸爸妈妈的情人节。
We got to fix this.
我们必须解决这个问题。
Listen, I don't want to be the voice of reason here,
听着，我不想在这里充当理智的声音，
but we have an assignment due Monday.
但我们有一个周一要交的作业。
This is our assignment.
这就是我们的作业。
We're gonna give Mom and Dad
我们要让爸爸妈妈
back the love of Valentine's Day that we took from them.
重新感受到我们夺走的情人节的爱的氛围。
Let's do it.
我们来做吧。
Yeah, time to save Valentime's.
是的，是时候拯救情人节了。
Okay, I've got a new assignment for you.
好的，我有一个新的任务给你。
Learn how to say Valentine's
学会如何用N发音说情人节。
with an N.
带上一个N。
Tine. Tine!
Tine。Tine！
Let it go, man.
算了吧，老兄。
It's just one letter.
就差一个字母。
[Dicky] The TV's throwing up.
[Dicky]电视在吐东西。
[Dawn] Ew.
[Dawn]哎呀。
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
♪ ♪
I hope my Valentine's date
我希望我的情人节约会
is as romantic as this.
能像这样浪漫。
Your parents are gonna love it.
你父母一定会喜欢的。
I hope so.
希望如此。
There's a lot riding on it.
这事关重大。
Yeah, our grade.
是啊，我们的成绩。
Since when do you care about grades?
你什么时候在乎过成绩了？
Huh, you're right. I don't.
嗯，你说得对。我不在乎。
Hey, this is about rekindling
嘿，这是为了重燃
Mom and Dad's Valentine's Day flame.
爸妈的情人节激情。
And getting a good grade.
还有拿个好成绩。
What is wrong with me?
我这是怎么了？
Here they come. Assume romance positions.
他们来了。摆出浪漫的姿势。
Oh, oh, oh!
哦，哦，哦！
Finally, Valentine's Day is almost over.
终于，情人节快结束了。
Ugh, only a couple more hours till we can put
呃，再过几个小时我们就可以
this holiday in the ground and shovel some dirt on it.
把这个节日埋了，再给它盖上土。
[all] Happy Valentine's Day!
大家情人节快乐！
Kids?
孩子们？
Look at our four little cupids!
看看我们这四个小丘比特！
Oh, I think you mean five.
哦，我想你说的是五个。
[laughing] Thank you!
谢谢！
What is all this?
这是怎么回事？
We just wanted to do something special for you two
我们只是想在情人节为你们俩做点特别的事。
on Valentine's Day.
欢迎来到哈珀爱情之家餐厅
So welcome to the Harper House of Love restaurant
还有咖啡馆、小酒馆和休息室。
and cafe, bistro, and lounge.
我们决定不了名字。
We couldn't decide on a name.
我觉得这个名字很完美。
I think that name is perfect.
很有效果。
- It's working. - Totally.
非常棒。
Okay, thanks for all your help, Josie,
好吧，乔西，谢谢你所有的帮助，但是已经很晚了。
but it's getting really late.
你最好去准备一下你的约会。
You better go get ready for your date.
你最好去准备你的约会。
I am ready.
我已经准备好了。
[all] Oh.
哦。
Is it my hair? My nails? My clothes?
是我的头发吗？我的指甲？我的衣服？
Let's just say the mess is still hot.
这么说吧，混乱依旧火爆。
May I show you to your table?
请问我可以带您到您的座位吗？
- Indeed. - Thank you.
当然。
We have you seated in the love section.
谢谢。
And while you enjoy your four-course meal--
我们为您安排在了爱情专区。
Three of which involve chocolate--
而当您享受您的四道菜大餐时——其中三道含有巧克力——
The food of love.
爱的食物。
[Dawn] Why not take a magical stroll down memory lane?
[Dawn] 何不沿着记忆的小径，来一次魔法的漫步？
I present: Mom and Dad's Book of Love Notes,
我呈现：《妈妈和爸爸的恋爱笔记》
Scrapbooks of Memories,
《记忆剪贴簿》
Chronicles of Questionable Hairdos,
《可疑发型的编年史》
and Icky Love Stuff.
以及《令人恶心的恋爱物品》
[Tom] Oh.
[Tom] 哦。
We couldn't decide on a name
我们也没能决定那个的名字
for that either.
[Dawn] 当你浏览这些时，
[Dawn] And while you look through that,
我们会准备你的下一道菜。
we'll get your next course.
我们将为您准备下一道菜。
Hint: it involves chocolate.
提示：它与巧克力有关。
The food of love.
爱的食物。
Wow.
哇。
The kids really put a lot of work into this.
孩子们真的在这上面下了很多功夫。
Oh, honey, look.
哦，亲爱的，看。
It's our first ice dancing competition.
这是我们的第一次冰舞比赛。
Look at that gorgeous hair.
看看那美丽的头发。
- Oh, thank you. - I was talking about me.
哦，谢谢你。
I miss it so much.
我非常怀念它。
Guys, it's working.
伙计们，有效果了。
We're rekindling the flame.
我们在重燃爱火。
[Anne] Huh, what is this?
[安妮] 这是什么？
"I love you. Love, A."
“我爱你。爱你的，A。”
Who's A?
A是谁？
You're A.
你就是A。
No, no, no. I'm an A, but I'm not this A.
不，不，不。我是A，但我不是这个A。
[gasps]
[倒吸一口气]
Is this from Angela?
这是安吉拉写的吗？
Who's Angela?
安吉拉是谁？
Your first girlfriend.
你的第一个女朋友。
Oh, Angela.
哦，安吉拉。
Mm-hmm.
嗯。
Tom, why would you keep a love letter
汤姆，你为什么留着前女友的情书？
from an old girlfriend?
（唐）哎呀。
[Dawn] Uh-oh.
亲爱的，我发誓，我以为我已经扔了那个。
Honey, I swear, I thought I threw that out.
（揉皱声）
[crumpling]
（叹气）
[sighs]
让我们看看这里面还有哪些美好的回忆。
Let's see what other beautiful memories
（倒吸气）
we have in here.
我们来看看这里还有哪些美好的回忆。
[gasps]
[倒抽一口气]
No, bup-bup-bup-bup- bup-bup-bup-bup-bup-bup.
不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不。
Bup.
不。
Isn't this a picture of your old boyfriend?
这不是你前男友的照片吗？
[with deep voice] Fireman Mike.
[用深沉的声音] 消防员迈克。
Have you seen how cute the dog is?
你看到那只狗有多可爱了吗？
[Dawn] Oh, we're losing them.
[Dawn] 哦，我们快失去他们了。
What are we gonna do?
我们该怎么办？
Teach them how to throw stuff out?
教他们怎么扔掉东西吗？
I got this. Chocolate fixes everything.
我来搞定。巧克力能解决一切。
[as Mr. T] I pity the fon-dude that don't eat this fondue.
[模仿Mr. T] 我可怜那些不吃这火锅的家伙。
[Dawn] Who wants to be the first to dip their strawberry
[Dawn] 谁想第一个把草莓蘸进融化的巧克力里？
in melted chocolate?
在融化的巧克力里？
I could've been a fireman too, Anne,
我本也可以成为消防员，Anne，
but you know I have a fear of Dalmatians.
但你知道我对达尔马提亚狗有恐惧。
Well, you certainly don't have a fear
嗯，你肯定不怕
of keeping old letters from A.
保留A的旧信件。
This isn't working.
这不管用。
Looks like it's time for Valen to work his magic.
看来是时候让Valen施展他的魔法了。
Not a real person, but just do it.
不是真人，但就照做吧。
[thwacks]
[啪]
[shouts]
[喊叫]
Ow!
哎哟！
[grunts]
[咕哝]
[gasps, screams]
[喘气，尖叫]
Hot chocolate! Hot chocolate!
热巧克力！热巧克力！
[both shouting]
[两人同时喊]
Hot wax! Hot wax!
热蜡！热蜡！
- Oh, no! - [shouting]
- 哦，不！ - [喊叫]
[ripping, grunting]
[撕裂声，呻吟声]
[all gasp]
[所有人倒抽一口气]
[gasps]
[倒抽一口气]
[screams]
[尖叫声]
Well, this couldn't get any worse.
唉，这不可能变得更糟了。
[fire crackling]
[火燃烧声]
[both scream]
[两人尖叫]
The couch!
沙发！
I think we rekindled the wrong flame.
我想我们点燃了错误的火焰。
- [shouts] - Somebody help me.
[呼喊] 有人来帮我。
Wait, what do we do?
等等，我们该怎么办？
[indistinct radio chatter]
（模糊的无线电通讯声）
Wow. That is hot.
哇，那真的很热。
I'm standing right here, Anne.
我就在这儿，安妮。
No, no. I meant the couch.
不，不，我是说那沙发。
Mm.
嗯。
We've seen a lot of Valentine's disasters,
我们见过很多情人节的灾难，
but...wow.
但是...哇。
[Dicky] We tried to give Mom and Dad something special,
（迪基）我们想给爸爸妈妈一个特别的礼物，
but all we did was ruin their Valentime's.
但我们只是毁了他们的情人节。
Excuse me.
对不起。
[screams]
[尖叫]
Sorry. You were saying?
抱歉。你刚才说什么？
[Dawn] [sighs]
[Dawn] [叹气]
Guys, Dicky's right.
伙计们，Dicky说得对。
We're the problem. We always have been.
我们才是问题所在。我们一直都是。
The nicest thing we can do for Mom and Dad
我们能为爸爸妈妈做的最好的事
is leave them alone for the rest of the night.
就是今晚剩下的时间让他们独自待着。
She's right. It's the only way to fix this.
她说得对。这是唯一能解决问题的办法。
[sighs] I'll write them a note.
[叹气] 我会给他们留张纸条。
[Dawn] Sorry we ruined Valentine's Day.
对不起，我们毁了情人节。
We're leaving. Be back later.
我们要走了。晚点回来。
[sighs]
叹气
[upbeat music]
轻快的音乐
♪ ♪
Oh, what a great way to do your assignment.
哦，这真是个完成作业的好方法。
Four little angels spreading Valentine's love.
四个小天使传播情人节的爱心。
[Dawn] I don't know about love,
关于爱，我不确定，
but we spread something.
但我们传播了些东西。
Mostly fire and hot wax.
主要是火和热蜡。
We kind of destroyed our parents' night.
我们好像毁了爸妈的夜晚。
And our couch.
还有我们的沙发。
Could we stay here for a while?
我们可以在这里待一会儿吗？
[laughs] Hi, kids.
[笑] 嗨，孩子们。
[all] Hey, Mr. and Mrs. Valentine.
[齐声] 嘿，瓦伦丁先生和夫人。
They wanted to know if they could hang out with us.
他们想知道是否可以和我们一起玩。
Hey, join us.
嘿，加入我们。
What better way to spend Valentine's
还有什么比和瓦伦丁一家一起度过情人节更好的方式呢？
than with the Valentines?
你不是想说瓦伦丁节吗？
Don't you mean Valentimes?
瓦伦丁节。
The Valentimes.
情人节。
That's it!
没错！
[thwacks]
[啪]
[cat meows]
[猫叫]
[Mae] Debbie!
[梅] 黛比！
[Mrs. Valentine] Oh, no!
[瓦伦丁夫人] 哦，不！
She's never been outside before!
她从没出过门！
She's heading towards the dog park!
她正朝狗公园跑去！
[dogs barking] [cat yowls]
[狗吠][猫嚎]
[Mr. Valentine] Ooh, it's officially the worst Valentine Valentine's ever!
[瓦伦丁先生] 哦，这正式成为有史以来最糟糕的情人节了！
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
♪ ♪
[panting]
[喘气声]
[grunting]
[咕哝声]
- Tom! - Hold on, Anne.
- 汤姆！ - 等等，安妮。
I'm just making sure the fire's out underneath the couch
我只是确保沙发下的火已经熄灭
that I easily picked up, just like the fireman.
我轻松地把它抬起来，就像消防员一样。
[chuckles]
[轻笑]
The kids ran away.
孩子们跑开了。
Huh?
嗯？
[shouts]
[大喊]
I think I located Dawn's phone.
我想我找到了Dawn的手机。
- Come on! - [grunts]
- 快来！ - [咕哝]
[grunts]
[咕哝]
[whimpers]
[呜咽]
Tom!
Tom！
[Anne] [grunts]
[Anne] [咕哝]
[Tom] How are you doing this?
[Tom] 你是怎么做到的？
[Anne] Fireman Mike taught me.
[Anne] 消防员Mike教我的。
[Tom] That hurts more than my foot, Anne.
[Tom] 这比我的脚还疼，Anne。
No way.
不可能。
You ordered us the Leaning Tower of Pizza?
你给我们点了斜塔披萨？
That's so romantic.
太浪漫了。
And if we finish it in 30 minutes,
如果我们能在30分钟内吃完，
it's free!
就免费！
[with Boston accent] You also get a car key chain that says,
（带波士顿口音）你还会得到一个车钥匙扣，上面写着，
I gobbled down the tower at DiPietro's Wall Oven Pizza.
我在DiPietro's壁炉披萨店吃掉了斜塔。
Okay, I didn't understand one word of that,
好吧，我一个字都没听懂，
but I'm having such a good time.
但我玩得很开心。
[Dicky] Oh, there she is.
哦，她来了。
She's already on her date. We can't bother her.
她已经在约会了。我们不能打扰她。
But we need the keys to the store.
但我们需要店里的钥匙。
Come on. Eat faster.
快点，吃快点。
I got this.
我搞定这个。
[thwacks]
（击打声）
Um...you just got shot in the head with an arrow.
呃...你刚被箭射中头部了。
- This is how they get you.
这就是他们抓住你的方式。
Keep focused.
保持专注。
I want that car key chain.
我想要那个车钥匙链。
[scoffs]
（嗤之以鼻）
Uh, excuse me one second.
呃，请稍等一下。
Hey, guys. What are you doing here?
嘿，伙计们。你们在这里做什么？
Wow. So that's what you went with?
哇。所以你们选择了这个？
What's wrong with it?
这有什么问题吗？
[all] Nothing!
没问题！
Okay, look.
好吧，听着。
We're sorry for interrupting your date,
我们很抱歉打断了你们的约会，
but we need your keys to the store.
但我们需要你们店里的钥匙。
Why?
为什么？
We're cursed.
我们被诅咒了。
We're like a black hole
我们就像一个黑洞
that sucks the love out of Valentine's Day.
把情人节的浪漫吸得一干二净。
So we need to get away from people for a little while
所以我们需要暂时远离人群
before we destroy anyone else's special day.
以免破坏了别人的特别日子。
Wait, cursed? Don't be silly.
等等，被诅咒？别开玩笑了。
There is no such thing as a curse.
哪有什么诅咒这种事。
[cat meows]
（猫叫声）
[shouting, barking]
（喊叫声，狗吠声）
What is this, a dog park?
这是什么地方，狗公园吗？
Hey, watch out for the wall oven.
嘿，小心那边的壁炉。
It'll scorch you.
它会烫伤你的。
Oops.
哎呀。
Okay, maybe you are a little cursed.
好吧，也许你有点被诅咒了。
Have you guys seen Debbie?
你们见过Debbie吗？
Debbie!
Debbie！
[Mr. Valentine] Stay away from our cat!
[Mr. Valentine] 离我们的猫远点！
[barking, meowing]
[狗叫，猫叫]
[panting]
[喘气]
Kids, are you okay?
孩子们，你们还好吗？
[Dawn] Mom, Dad, don't come near us!
[Dawn] 妈妈，爸爸，别靠近我们！
Why did you run away?
你们为什么要逃跑？
We're cursed!
我们被诅咒了！
We've been going door to door,
我们一直在挨家挨户地走，
destroying love wherever we go.
走到哪儿就破坏哪儿的爱情。
We've ruined Valentime's Day for you
自从我们出生以来，
every year since we've been born.
每年都毁了你们的情人节。
Did he say "time's"?
他刚才是说“时间的”吗？
You haven't ruined anything.
你们没有毁掉任何东西。
Mom, you don't have to lie. We saw the tape.
妈妈，你不用撒谎。我们看到了录像带。
The one from when you were preg-meant with us.
就是你们怀我们时的那盘录像带。
You mean pregnant?
你是说怀孕？
You guys wanted to have us, right?
你们想要有我们，对吧？
Of course we did.
当然我们想要。
So you meant to be preg.
所以你是故意怀孕的。
Preg-meant.
故意怀孕。
Anyway, we heard you guys say
不管怎样，我们听到你们说
we ruined Valentine's Day forever.
我们毁了情人节永远。
[both] Oh.
哦。
Did you hear us say anything else?
你们还听到我们说别的什么吗？
No, we turned it off.
没有，我们关掉了。
Okay, well, why don't we go home
好吧，那我们为什么不回家
and watch the rest of the tape?
然后看剩下的录像带呢？
So many spots.
这么多地方。
[whimpers] Ow. Ow. Ow.
哎哟。哎哟。哎哟。
Carry me, Anne!
背我，安妮！
[Anne] Come on.
来吧。
[Tom] All right.
好吧。
Everybody, grab a root beer.
大家，拿一瓶根啤。
[Anne] [clears throat]
（安妮）（清嗓子）
I think there's a little bit more
我觉得这录像带上还有
on this tape that you need to see.
在这盘磁带上还有一些你需要看的内容。
[Tom] Wow, this is really happening.
[Tom] 哇，这真的发生了。
We're having quadruplets.
我们要生四胞胎。
You know what this means, Tom?
你知道这意味着什么吗，Tom？
Valentine's Day is ruined. Forever.
情人节毁了。永远。
[Tom] It sure is.
[Tom] 确实如此。
No Valentine's Day could ever possibly live up to this one.
没有任何一个情人节能比得上这一个。
I'm so happy, Tom.
我太高兴了，Tom。
[Tom] [laughs]
[Tom] [笑]
Me too.
我也是。
In fact, I am four times happier
事实上，我现在比我想象中还要快乐四倍。
than I ever thought I could be.
比我曾经以为的还要快乐。
[all] Aw!
啊！
[all] Ew!
呃！
[Tom] And that is why we don't celebrate Valentine's Day.
这就是为什么我们不庆祝情人节。
Any gift we gave each other
我们互赠的任何礼物
would be nothing compared to you guys.
与你相比都显得微不足道。
So we're not cursed.
所以我们并没有被诅咒。
We didn't ruin Valentine's Day.
我们没有毁掉情人节。
Of course you didn't.
当然没有。
You're not even mad about the eyebrow?
你甚至不介意眉毛的事吗？
Nah, nothing a little black marker can't fix.
不，一点黑色马克笔就能搞定。
Huh?
嗯？
-Um...
嗯...
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
And then, after our parents showed us a videotape,
然后，在我们父母给我们看了一盘录像带之后，
it all made sense.
一切都解释得通了。
We all know what you're gonna ask.
我们都知道你想问什么。
This is a videotape.
这是一盘录像带。
It's how they used to watch movies in the olden days.
这是他们过去在古老时代看电影的方式。
[all] Ooh.
哦。
[Dawn] So what we learned from all this is,
我们从这一切中学到的是，
Valentine's Day isn't about
情人节不是关于
who gets the most cards or candy.
谁收到最多的卡片或糖果。
It's about showing the people you care for
而是关于向你在乎的人展示
how much they mean to you.
他们对你有多重要。
Even if you end up with a burnt couch.
即使你最终得到一个烧焦的沙发。
And a lifetime ban from DiPietro's Wall Oven Pizza.
以及对DiPietro's壁炉披萨的终身禁令。
And what I learned is, Valentime's Day
而我学到的是，情人节
is actually called Valentine's Day.
实际上被称为情人节。
Thank you.
谢谢。
Well, on to Paint Patrick's Day.
好吧，接下来是画帕特里克的节日。
And before we know it, it'll be time for the Easter Buddy.
在我们意识到之前，复活节伙伴的时间就要到了。
I'm just kidding.
我只是在开玩笑。
April Foods!
四月愚人节！
Excuse me.
对不起。
[Ricky screams]
（瑞奇尖叫）
- ♪ ♪
♪ ♪
- [whistling melody]
（吹口哨旋律）
♪ ♪
- [vocalizing]
♪ Yeah ♪
[vocalizing]
- ♪